The fact that we have Black folks who find themselves unable to support themselves because
of the United States government and its ways, the fact that we have Black cultural centers,
the fact that we have Black artisans, the fact that Black identity is under fire and
you haven't seen man one Black billionaire say anything about an initiative or even a
desire to create an initiative to support this, to challenge it, et cetera, should trouble
you.
You see, the thing about the whole billionaire thing is that when you are a billionaire,
you have more money than you know what to do with.
That's not like a figure of speech.
It's an actual thing.
You have enough money than some countries possess.
Thus, you have the ability to create infrastructure that the government does not create.
Now, for anyone who says, well, this country is not racist and it's Black people's problem.
Um, okay.
So then if it's our problem and we solve it, then what's the issue?
So imagine if the Black Panthers, who literally were a volunteer-based organization, were able
to create senior centers, even an extermination service, sickle cell clinics, free lunch programs,
tutoring, et cetera.
That was all done to fill gaps that the U.S. government had created and Black people were falling into.
Now, instead of saying, good job, we didn't have to do it.
Y'all did it yourselves.
They said, oh, no, we can't have Black people like excelling.
And they shut it down.
However, time is advanced and we have enough multimillionaires and Black billionaires to
try again.
And if we coalition build, we got enough billionaire and multimillionaire Asians, Indians, brown
folks, et cetera, to be able to do this.
So when we talk about the fact that the government isn't doing what it's supposed to, it's not.
However, when we talk about capitalism and we talk about the necessity to get out from
under it, we have enough multimillionaire and billionaires that can create a planned economy.
We have enough folks that have actually benefited greatly from capitalism.
And many folks say, why should they have to spend their money?
Because they have it to spend.
They're not even paying taxes the way they should be.
So this is the least they could do.
There have been several times where it has been tycoons of industry that have saved this
nation from going under.
How about this time?
Instead of saving the government, they save the people.
And if you're not going to use the money to help the people,
at least help the planet because it's your friends that are killing it.
And we still own it.
Support a real one.